{
    "id": "b60cca769aea412e979b8f74420f038c",
    "title": "Words Confused Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "As his children watched, the old man ......................... his eyes for the last time.",
            "description": "We prefer close for slow movements. ",
            "answers": [
                "shut",
                "closed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her garments are made of the best ........................",
            "description": "Cloth is the material used for making clothes. The nouns material and fabric can also be used instead of cloth. ",
            "answers": [
                "cloth",
                "fabric",
                "material",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "'I suppose the movie wasn't very interesting.' '.............................., it was fantastic.'",
            "description": "On the contrary is an expression used to contradict. On the other hand is used to give the other side of a question.",
            "answers": [
                "On the contrary",
                "On the other hand",
                "By contrast"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie wasn't very interesting but ............................, its cinematography was superb.",
            "description": "On the contrary is an expression used to contradict. On the other hand is used to give the other side of a question.",
            "answers": [
                "on the contrary",
                "on the other hand",
                "by contrast"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We live in ..................... just outside California.",
            "description": "The country is the opposite of the town.",
            "answers": [
                "country",
                "a country",
                "the country"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am quite ......................... in politics.",
            "description": "If you are uninterested in something, you have no interest in it. ",
            "answers": [
                "uninterested",
                "disinterested"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A banker should be able to give ......................... advice.",
            "description": "Disinterested means unbiased. ",
            "answers": [
                "uninterested",
                "disinterested",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you .......................... doing the laundry yet?",
            "description": "When finish is used with an object, it means complete. ",
            "answers": [
                "ended",
                "finished",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ........................ his days in an old age home.",
            "description": "To end days is to die.",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "ended",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Our new apartment has a spare bedroom for ...................... visitors.",
            "description": "The word eventual is not used to express the idea of possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "eventual",
                "possible",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The child didn't want to sleep but ........................ I got her to bed.",
            "description": "Eventually is used to say that something happens after a long time or after a lot of effort. ",
            "answers": [
                "eventually",
                "at the end",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a very ......................... laugh.",
            "description": "The word feminine is used to refer to qualities that are typical of women. ",
            "answers": [
                "feminine",
                "female"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}